beget.ru 2018-09-04

# Privacy Policy. BeGet

* * *

BeGet GmbH (BeGet) has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy to our customers and users of this website. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which BeGet GmbH (BeGet) uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its website. This website is not directed at children under 18 years of age. 

**Information Collected**   
BeGet may request or collect personal information from online users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information. The data we collect is information that identifies you personally, such as:   
\- Your name   
\- E-mail address   
\- Postal address   
\- Telephone and telefax numbers   
\- URL   
\- Credit card information   
\- Other billing information 

BeGet may also collect information about how users access the website using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computers hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browsers help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by BeGet to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Persistent cookies may be used by BeGet to store whether, for example, you want your password remembered or not, and other information. Cookies used on the BeGet website do not contain personally identifiable information. 

**Log Files**   
Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Information use**   
BeGet may use the personally identifiable information collected by BeGet to contact customers regarding products and services offered by BeGet and, to the extent the user has agreed to it, by its trusted affiliates, independent contractors and business partners. We may also use this information and share it with trusted third parties for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts, including, without limitation, for purposes of customer reviews (such as for the utilization of programs like Google Seller Ratings). BeGet will not sell or otherwise share this information with a third party for a third party's marketing purposes, unless you specifically authorize such information sharing. BeGet may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, only statistical information will be disclosed and personally identifiable data will be kept strictly confidential. In case BeGet is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners. BeGet may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or manipulate data received by BeGet from its customers. In all such cases, third party service providers will be required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as BeGet and they will be prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy. 

**Disclosing Information**   
_Partners and Sponsors._ Some of our products or services are offered or promoted to our customers in conjunction with a partner or sponsor, or another brand or company within our corporate family. We may share your information with these parties to offer the product or service or to facilitate your use of additional amenities included with your hosting account. For example, one of our partners may provide services to you based on links that you access from your control panel.   
We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to potential partners, reputable third parties and other companies or brands within our corporate family. We will only share your information with third parties that agree to maintain your information in confidence and to use it solely for purposes of providing the product or service as agreed to by BeGet. 

_Service Providers._ We may transfer (or otherwise make available) your personal information to third parties that help us provide our services or provide services on our behalf. For example, we may use service providers to authorize and process payments, administer surveys, or run promotions. Your personal information may be maintained and processed by our third party service providers. Our service providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose personal information for their own marketing or other purposes. 

_Online Advertisements._ We do not share personally identifiable information about individual customers with advertisers. We may display online advertisements and we may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our customers that we collect through the registration process or through online surveys and promotions with certain advertisers. In some instances, we use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. For example, an advertiser may tell us the audience they want to reach (e.g., males between 20 and 40 years of age) and provide us with an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display the advertisement to the intended audience. 

_Customer Surveys._ We may share customer information obtained from customer surveys within HostGator and our corporate family, and with trusted third parties to develop or provide products and services that we believe would be of interest to our customers. 

_Domain Registration._ In certain jurisdictions or pursuant to the rules of the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN") or certain registries, the contact information you provide to register a domain name ("Domain Name Registration Information") has to be made available and accessible to the public through a "WHOIS" search. The WHOIS database is a publicly accessible database that lists the Domain Name Registration Information for a particular domain name, the name server(s) to which the domain name points, and the domain name's creation and expiration date. The Domain Name Registration Information you provide is hosted by us or a third party service provider and is made available to the public through WHOIS searches. At times, customers may receive solicitations that result from searches of the publicly available WHOIS database by other companies or individuals. Any such solicitations or SPAM do not come from BeGet and we do not control the use of WHOIS information by third parties. Further, pursuant to ICANN rules, BeGet is required to make WHOIS data available to any third party that enters into a bulk access agreement. While ICANN allows individuals to opt-out (using the account management panel, domain management console or similar service) of having their WHOIS information made available to third parties through bulk access, companies, such as ours, businesses, and other organizations do not have the ability to opt-out of having their information made available to a third party that enters a bulk access agreement. We may also deposit your Domain Name Registration Information with a third-party escrow provider to comply with ICANN requirements. 

_Law Enforcement and Special Cases._ BeGet cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about users upon a valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect your property and rights, or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to stop activity that we consider illegal or unethical. 

**Special Offers and Updates**   
Our customers and users will occasionally receive newsletters or e-mails with information on products, services, or special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, BeGet gives them the opportunity to opt-out from receiving these types of communications. 

**Service Announcements**   
On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement, if, for instance, our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature. 

**Third Party Websites**   
The BeGet website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that BeGet is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The BeGet Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by BeGet. 

**Maintenance of Information**   
The information provided to BeGet is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by BeGet. BeGet employs industry-standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur, we make every effort to prevent such occurrences. Any other particularly sensitive information, such as credit card numbers collected for commercial transactions, is encrypted prior to transmission by you to BeGet. 

**Your Responsibility**   
You are responsible for the security of your Customer ID and passwords. Make sure you keep them in a safe place and do not share them with others. Always remember to log out after your session ends to ensure that others cannot access your private personal information. You should take this precaution even if you are not using a public computer, but even when using your private computer in your home. 

**Data Security**   
BeGet uses technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alternation or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control. BeGet uses security measures including and not limited to: physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. All sensitive information is collected on a secure server. When we ask customers or users to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology. 

**Contacting Us** BeGet encourages individuals covered by this Privacy Policy to raise any concerns about our processing of personal information by contacting BeGet at the address below.: Otto-Suhr-Allee 27, 10585 Berlin, Deutschland   
BeGet will seek to resolve any concerns. 

**Questions** Any questions concerning this Privacy Policy may be directed by e-mail to [manager@beget.com](mailto:manager@beget.com). To report abuse, please send an e-mail to [abuse@beget.com](mailto:abuse@beget.com).
